Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series X. Faculty and Staff
  - Lists/Directories, 1950-1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lists/Directories, 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lists/Directories, 1973-n.d. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Roster of Special Interests, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Code of Ethics, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Position Descriptions (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Profiles, ca.1980's-n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Profiles, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Profiles, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Workshop on Teaching, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Senior Faculty Seminars, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Staff Sercice Recognition Ceremony (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Newsletters-"Schurman News and Views", 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - "VIP:Veterinary Information for Personel", 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Faculty and Staff Roster, 1975, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Millenium Time Capsule (Box 8)
  - Biographical Files (including photographs)
    - Faculty
      - Centennial faculty (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Abou-Madi, Noha (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Acland, Gregory (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Aguirre, Gustavo (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Ainsworth, Dorothy (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Akey, Bruce (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Andrews, Edwin Joseph (Box 23, Folder 7)
        1941-
      - Antczak, Douglas F. (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Appel, Max J. (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Appel, Max J. (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Appleton, Judith (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Asmus, Henry (Box 23, Folder 12)
        1875-1939
        See also Memorial Statement
      - Avery, Roger (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Babish, John (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Baggs, Raymond (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Bailey, Michele M. (Smith) (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Baines, Joel N. (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Baker, Donald Wyckoff (Box 23, Folder 18-19)
        1899-1978
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History collection (Ep Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Baker, Donald Wyckoff (Box 23, Folder 20)
        Oversized photo
      - Baker, James Andrew (Box 23, Folder 21)
        1910-1975
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326
      - Baker, James Andrew (Box 23, Folder 22)
        Items were removed from a scrapbook created by Jeannie Griffith
      - Baldwin, Charles (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Ball, Barry (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Barr, Margaret (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - Barr, Stephen Charles (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Barrett, Robert B. (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - Bell, Robin G. (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - Benner, James W. (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - Benson, Thomas F. (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - Bentinck-Smith, John (Box 23, Folder 31)
        1919-2005
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Memorial Statement
      - Bergman, Emmett Norlin (Box 23, Folder 32)
        1929-1989
      - Beyenbach, Klaus (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - Birch, Raymond Russell (Box 23, Folder 34)
        1881-1959
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-525; Memorial Statement
      - Bistner, Stephen Ira (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - Blue, Julia Tait (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - Blue, Murray (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - Bolton, Gary Robert (Box 23, Folder 38)
        1942-1982
      - Bowman, Dwight D. (Box 23, Folder 39-40)
      - Bowser, Paul R. (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Boyer, Clyde I., Jr. (Box 23, Folder 42)
        1913-2003
      - Brasmer, Timothy H. (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - Brooks, Marjory (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - Brown, H. Alex (Box 23, Folder 45)
        1960-
      - Bruner, Dorsey William (Box 23, Folder 46)
        1906-1996
      - Brunett, Earl Louis (Box 23, Folder 47)
        1898-1943
      - Brunner, Michael Arthur (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - Brunson, David B. (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - Bunch, Sharon (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - Buckles, Elizabeth L. (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - Burnett, Samuel Howard (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - Calnek, Bruce Wixson (Box 23, Folder 53-54)
        1932-
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History collection 24-4-3349; Papers 24-2-3346
      - Campbell, Samuel Gordon (Box 23, Folder 55-56)
        1933-1997
      - Carlisle, James G. (Box 23, Folder 57)
        1930-
      - Carmichael, Leland E. (Box 23, Folder 58-61)
        See also Papers 24-4-3388
      - Casarett, Alison P. (Box 24, Folder 1)
        1930-2002
      - Casey, James W. (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Castleman, Benjamin (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Center, Sharon A. (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Center, Sharon A. (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Cerione, Richard A. (Box 24, Folder 6-7)
      - Chang, Yung-Fu (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Cho, Jane (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Clark, Lawrence (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Cockerell, Gary L. (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Coggins, Leroy (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Cole, Randall Knight (Box 24, Folder 13)
        1912-2006
        See also Oral History collection 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Collier, Michael A. (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Collins, Ruth N. (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Comar, Cyril L. (Box 24, Folder 16)
        1914-1979
      - Concannon, Patrick W. (Box 24, Folder 17)
        1941-2015
      - Cook, Vanessa L. (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Coonrod, Scott (Box 24, Folder 19)
      - Cooper, Barry J. (Box 24, Folder 20)
      - Corradino, Robert A. (Box 24, Folder 21)
      - Cowen, B. (Box 24, Folder 22)
      - Cummings, John Francis (Box 24, Folder 23-25)
        1936-1996
      - Cypess, Raymond H. (Box 24, Folder 26)
      - Daels, Peter (Box 24, Folder 27)
      - Danks, Arthur Gordon (Box 24, Folder 28)
        1906-1989
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection (EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Davidson, ? (Box 24, Folder 29)
      - Davisson, Robin L. (Box 24, Folder 30)
      - DeBoy, Jack (Box 24, Folder 31)
      - Delahanty, Donald Dee (Box 24, Folder 32)
        1923-1975
      - de Lahunta, Alexander (Box 24, Folder 33-37)
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3349; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - de Noronha, Fernando (Box 24, Folder 38)
        1924-2010
      - Dhupa, Nishi (Box 24, Folder 39)
      - Dietert, Rodney R. (Box 24, Folder 40)
      - Dill, Stephen G. (Box 24, Folder 41)
      - Dillingham, Lloyd (Box 24, Folder 42)
      - Dinsmore, Paige (Box 24, Folder 43)
      - Divers, Thomas J. (Box 24, Folder 44)
      - Dobson, Alan (Box 24, Folder 45-46)
        1928-
      - Dougherty, Ellsworth (Box 24, Folder 47)
      - Dougherty, Robert W. (Box 24, Folder 48)
      - Dubovi, Edward J. (Box 24, Folder 49)
      - Ducharme, Normand Guy (Box 24, Folder 50)
        1957-
      - Dukes, Henry Hugh (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
        1895-1987
        See also Papers 6640: Oral History Collection (EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Dunn, Henry O. (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Dunny, G. (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Dye, Joseph A. (Box 25, Folder 6)
        1892-1966
      - Dykes, Nathan Leonard (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Erb, Hollis Nancy (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Evans, Howard Edward (Box 25, Folder 9-16)
        1922-
        See also Papers 24-2-1870; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Fabricant, Catherine Grenci (Box 25, Folder 17)
        1919-2001
      - Fabricant, Julius (Box 25, Folder 18)
        19??-2011
        See also Oral History Collection 24-4-3349
      - Farnum, Cornelia E. (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Farrow, Brian R. H. (Box 25, Folder 20)
      - Fewtrell, Clare Mary Sanders (Box 25, Folder 21)
        1948-
      - Field, Lincoln E. (Box 25, Folder 22)
      - Fincher, Myron Gustin (Box 25, Folder 23-24)
        1898-1981
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-802; Memorial Statement
      - Fish, Pierre Augustine (Box 25, Folder 25)
        1865-1931
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-1677; Memorial Statement
      - Flanders, James A. (Box 25, Folder 26)
      - Foerster, Sonia Hernandez (Box 25, Folder 27)
        1969-
      - Foote, Robert H. (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Fortune, Joanne (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Fox, Francis Henry (Box 25, Folder 30-33)
        1923-2015
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Frank, Diane (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Fregin, Frederick (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - French, Tracy Warren (Box 25, Folder 35)
        1951-2009
      - Frost, James Nathan (Box 25, Folder 36)
        1885-1949
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-1204; Memorial Statement
      - Fubini, Susan Lawson (Box 25, Folder 37)
      - Fulmer, Curtis (Box 25, Folder 38)
      - Gage, Simon Henry (Box 26, Folder 1)
        1851-1944
        See also Gage Family Papers 4937; Memorial Statement
      - Gans, Joseph H. (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Gasteiger, Edgar L. (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Geary, Jack Charles (Box 26, Folder 4)
        1920-1992
      - Gelzer, Anna (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Georgi, Jay Robert (Box 26, Folder 6)
        19??-2015
      - Georgi, Marion E. Schott (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Gilbert, Robert Owen (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Gillespie, James Howard (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
        See also Papers 24-2-3293
      - Gilman, Herbert Lester (Box 26, Folder 11)
        1895-1982
      - Gilmour, Robert Fulton, Jr. (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Gleed, Robin Desmond (Box 26, Folder 13)
        1953-
      - Glickman, Lawrence T. (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Goldstein, Richard S. (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Gonzalez, Ruben Nestor (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Goodrich, Laura R. (Box 26, Folder 17)
        1965-
      - Gould, Willard Joseph, III "Jay" (Box 26, Folder 18)
        1949-
      - Graham, David Lee (Box 26, Folder 19)
        1939-
      - Griesemer, Richard A. (Box 26, Folder 20)
        1929-
      - Grohn, Yrjo Tapio (Box 26, Folder 21)
      - Guan, Jun-Lin (Box 26, Folder 22)
      - Guard, Charles L. (Box 26, Folder 23)
      - Gunn, Teresa Monique (Box 26, Folder 24)
        1968-
      - Habel, Robert E. (Box 26, Folder 25)
        See also Oral History Collection 24-04-3349
      - Hackett, Mary Susan (Box 26, Folder 26)
      - Hackett, Richard P. (Box 26, Folder 27)
      - Hagan, William Arthur (Box 26, Folder 28)
        1893-1963
        See also Papers 24-1-482 and Memorial Statement
      - Hall, Charles (Box 26, Folder 29)
      - Hansel, William (Box 26, Folder 30)
        1918-
      - Harkins, Daniel (Box 26, Folder 31)
      - Harvey, Harold Jay (Box 26, Folder 32)
        1947-
      - Haussler, Kevin (Box 26, Folder 33)
      - Hayden, Charles Ernest (Box 26, Folder 34)
        1881-1948
      - Haynes, Nelson Bruce (Box 26, Folder 35)
        1926-
      - Henion, John D. (Box 26, Folder 36)
      - Hermanson, John W. (Box 26, Folder 37)
      - Hill, Jonathan R. (Box 26, Folder 38)
      - Hillman, Robert Bryant (Box 26, Folder 39)
      - Hintz, Harold "Skip" (Box 26, Folder 40)
      - Hitchner, Stephen B. (Box 26, Folder 41)
      - Hopkins, Grant Sherman (Box 26, Folder 42)
        1865-1952
      - Hornbuckle, William E. (Box 26, Folder 43)
      - Holzinger, Edwin A. (Box 26, Folder 44)
      - Houpt, Katherine Albro (Box 26, Folder 45)
      - Houpt, Thomas Richard (Box 26, Folder 46)
        1925-2003
      - Hutt, Frederick Bruce (Box 26, Folder 47)
        1897-1991
      - Huxtable, Clive Rowan Ralston (Box 26, Folder 48)
        1940-
      - Jacobson, Richard H. (Box 26, Folder 49)
        1942-
      - Johnson, Seth Darwin (Box 26, Folder 50)
        1903-1975
        See also Alumni file 25-4-3326
      - Jubb, Kenneth V. (Box 26, Folder 51)
      - Kaderly, Robert (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Kahrs, Robert Frederick (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Kallfelz, Francis Anthony (Box 27, Folder 3)
        1938-
      - Kare, Morley R. (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Kemen, Mathias John, Jr. (Box 27, Folder 5)
        1926-2009
      - Kenney, Robert M. (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Kern, Thomas J. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - King, John McKain (Box 27, Folder 8)
        1927-
      - Kingsbury, John M. (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Kirk, Robert Warren (Box 27, Folder 10-14)
        1922-2011
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-3372; Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Kollias, George V., II (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Kotlikoff, Michael I. (Box 27, Folder 16)
        1951-
      - Kradel, David Charles (Box 27, Folder 17)
        1930-2006
      - Krook. Lennart P. (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Law, James (Box 27, Folder 19-22)
        1838-1921
        See also Paper 24-1-3329, Memorial Statement
      - Lee, David E. (Box 27, Folder 22)
      - Lee, Kyu Myong (Box 27, Folder 23)
      - Leibovitz, Louis (Box 27, Folder 24)
        1921-1998
      - Lein, Donald Henry (Box 27, Folder 25)
        1933-
      - Lengemann, Frederick W. (Box 27, Folder 26)
      - Leonard, Ellis Pierson (Box 27, Folder 27-28)
        1904-1991
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-2645; Memorial Statement
      - Levine, Pincus Philip (Box 27, Folder 29)
        1907-1979
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection ( EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Levine, Roy A. (Box 27, Folder 30)
      - Lewis, Robert M. (Box 27, Folder 31)
        1937-2011
      - Lindquist, Wesley (Box 27, Folder 32)
      - Lindmark, Donald G. (Box 27, Folder 33)
      - Little, Thomas (Box 27, Folder 34)
      - Loew, Ellis R. (Box 27, Folder 35)
      - Loew, Franklin Martin (Box 27, Folder 36)
        1939-2003
      - Lowe, John Edward (Box 27, Folder 37)
        1935-
      - Looney, Andrea Lynn (Box 27, Folder 38)
      - Lopez, Jorge (Box 27, Folder 39)
      - Lucio-Martinez, Benjamin (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Ludders, John William (Box 27, Folder 41)
        1944-
      - Lust, George (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - MacCauley, Alan (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - MacCoy, Douglas M. (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - MacLeod, James N. (Box 27, Folder 45)
        1959-
      - Manor, Danny (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Marmor, Michael (Box 27, Folder 47)
      - Marquis, Helene (Box 27, Folder 48)
      - Maylin, George A. (Box 27, Folder 49)
      - Mazza, Paul (Box 27, Folder 50)
      - McCashin, Fred B. (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - McClure, Robert C. (Box 27, Folder 52)
      - McDonough, Patrick L. (Box 27, Folder 53)
      - McDonough, Sean (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - McEntee, Kenneth B. (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
        1921-2005
      - McEntee, Margaret Colleen (Box 28, Folder 4)
        1955-
      - McGregor, Douglas D. (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Melby, Edward Carlos, Jr. (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Messick, Joanne B. (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Meyers-Wallen, Vicki N. (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Milks, Howard Jay (Box 28, Folder 9)
        1879-1954
      - Miller, Malcolm Eugene (Box 28, Folder 10)
        1909-1960
      - Miller, William H., Jr. (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Minor, Ronald R. (Box 28, Folder 12)
        1936-
      - Mizer, Linda (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Mohammed, Hussni O. (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Moise, Nancy Sydney (Box 28, Folder 15)
        1954-
      - Moore, Veranus Alva (Box 28, Folder 16)
        1859-1931
        See also Papers 24-1-119 and Memorial Statement
      - Morrisey, James K. (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Murphy, James M. (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Mutalib, Ahmed (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Nangeroni, Louis Lindo (Box 28, Folder 20)
        1918-1989
      - Naqi, Syed (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Nathanielsz, Peter W. (Box 28, Folder 22-23)
      - Nikitin, Alexander Yu (Box 28, Folder 24)
      - Nixon, Alan J. (Box 28, Folder 25)
      - Njaa, Bradley L. (Box 28, Folder 26)
      - Noden, Drew M. (Box 28, Folder 27)
      - Norcross, Neil L. (Box 28, Folder 28)
      - Nowak, Linda M. (Box 28, Folder 29)
      - Nussbaum, Sidney Robert (Box 28, Folder 30)
        1924-1998
      - Nydam, Daryl V. (Box 28, Folder 31)
      - O'Connor, M. (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - Olafson, Peter (Box 28, Folder 33-34)
        1897-1985
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-2234; Memorial Statement
      - Olander, Harvey J. (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - Osterrieder, Nikolaus (Box 28, Folder 36)
      - Oswald, Robert E. (Box 28, Folder 37)
      - Page, Rodney Lee (Box 28, Folder 38)
      - Panciera, Roger G. (Box 28, Folder 39)
      - Pauli, Benedict U. (Box 28, Folder 40)
      - Parrish, Colin Ross (Box 28, Folder 41)
      - Peckham, Malcolm Curtis (Box 28, Folder 42)
        1920-
      - Phemister, Robert D. (Box 28, Folder 43-45)
        See also Alumni File 24-4-3326
      - Playter, Robert (Box 28, Folder 46)
      - Pollock, Roy Van Horn (Box 28, Folder 47)
      - Poppensiek, George Charles (Box 28, Folder 48-49)
      - Poppensiek, George Charles (Box 29, Folder 1-8)
      - Postle, Donald S. (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Quick, Charles B. (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Quimby, Fred William (Box 29, Folder 11)
        1945-
      - Randolph, John F. (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Rassnick, Kenneth M. (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Ray, Jarna (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Rebhun, William Charles (Box 29, Folder 15)
        1947-1999
      - Reimers, Thomas J. (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Rendano, Victor Thomas, Jr. (Box 29, Folder 17)
        1946-
      - Reynolds, Arleigh J. (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Richards, James R. (Box 29, Folder 19)
        1948-2007
      - Rickard, Charles Glenwood (Box 29, Folder 20)
        1922-1993
        See also Alumni File 24-4-3326; Papers 24-7-3546; Memorial Statement
      - Riis, Ronald C. (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Roberts, Stephen James (Box 29, Folder 22-24)
        1915-2005
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 24-2-2903; Memorial Statement
      - Robertshaw, David (Box 29, Folder 25)
        1934-
      - Ross, George E., Jr. (Box 29, Folder 26)
      - Rossiter, Christine (Box 29, Folder 27)
      - Russell, David George (Box 29, Folder 28)
        1956-
      - Sack, Wolfgang Otto (Box 29, Folder 29)
        1928-2005
      - Saidla, John E. (Box 29, Folder 30)
      - Scartlett, Janet [Scarlett-Kranz, Janet] (Box 29, Folder 31)
      - Schat, Karel Antoni (Box 29, Folder 32)
      - Schermerhorn, Thomas (Box 29, Folder 33)
      - Schlafer, Donald Hughes (Box 29, Folder 34)
      - Schukken, Ynte Hein (Box 29, Folder 35)
      - Schryver, Herbert Francis (Box 29, Folder 36)
        See Also Alumni file 24-4-3326
      - Schwark, Wayne Stanley (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Scidmore, Marci A. (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Scott, Danny W. (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Scott, Fredric Winthrop (Box 30, Folder 4)
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Oral History Collection 24-4-3349
      - Scrivani, Peter Vincent (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Sears, Philip (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Seeger, Christoph (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Sellers, Alvin F. (Box 30, Folder 8)
        1917-2008
      - Sevoian, Martin (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Sharp, Geoffrey W. G. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Sheffy, Ben E. (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Shelly, Sonjia (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Shin, Sang Jae (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Shively, James N. (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Short, Charles Everette (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
      - Simpson, Kenneth William (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Slauson, David Owen (Box 30, Folder 18)
        1943-
      - Smith, Donald Frederick (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Smith, Mary Cole (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Spaulding, Glen L. (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Spitzbergen, Jan (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Stehman, Susan (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Stephenson, Hadley Carruthers (Box 30, Folder 24)
        1893-1976
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3226; Memorial Statement
      - Stevens, Charles Edward (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Stinson, Al W. (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Straw, Barbara (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Stokol, Tracy (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Suarez, Susan S. (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Summer, William A. (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Sunderville, Earl (Box 30, Folder 31)
        1886-1958
      - Summers, Brian Alan (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Suter, Maja (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - Tamke, Patricia (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - Tapper, Daniel N. (Box 30, Folder 35)
      - Tasker, John Baker, Jr. (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Tennant, Bud C. (Box 30, Folder 37-38)
      - Thompson, John C., Jr. (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - Todhunter, Rory James (Box 30, Folder 40)
        1952-
      - Torres, Alfonso (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - Trotter, Eric J. (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - Udall, Denny Hammond (Box 30, Folder 43)
        1874-1955
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 6641; Memorial Statement
      - Utermohlen, Virginia (Box 30, Folder 44)
      - Valentine, Beth A. (Box 30, Folder 45)
      - Visek, Willard J. (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - Volkmann, Dietert Hans (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - Wade, Susan E. (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - Walton, Donna (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - Wasserman, Robert H. (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - Wasserman, Robert H. (Box 30, Folder 51)
        See also Papers; 21-40-3519; Oral History Collection 24-4-3349
      - Wassom, Donald (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - Weiland, Gregory Arthur (Box 30, Folder 53)
        1950-
      - Wentworth, Richard A. (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - Wertz, Etta (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - Whittaker, Gary R. (Box 30, Folder 56)
      - White, Karl Karey, III (Box 30, Folder 57)
      - White, Maurice Edward "Pete" (Box 30, Folder 58)
      - Whitlock, John Hendrick (Box 30, Folder 59-60)
        1913-1994
        See also Papers 24-2-2223; Memorial Statement
      - Whitlock, Robert Henry (Box 30, Folder 61)
      - Williams, Walter Long (Box 30, Folder 62)
        1856-1945
        See also Oral History Collection (EP Leonard) 24-4-3349; Memorial Statement
      - Wimsatt, William Abell (Box 30, Folder 63)
        1917-1985
      - Winand, Nina J. (Box 30, Folder 64)
      - Winter, Alexander Joseph (Box 30, Folder 65)
        See also Oral History Collection (tape only) 24-4-3349
      - Woodie, James Brett (Box 30, Folder 66)
      - Woods, Gordon (Box 30, Folder 67)
      - Wootton, John F. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Wurster, Nancy Burton (Box 31, Folder 2)
        1941-2006
      - Yeager, Amy (Dietze, Amy E. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Yen, Andrew (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - York, Charles J. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Zadoks, Ruth (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Zeissig, Alexander (Box 31, Folder 7)
        1901-1974
        See also Alumni file 24-4-3326; Papers 6642
      - Zimmer, James Francis (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Personnel
      - Residents, Interns (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Visiting Professors, Adjuncts, Fellows, Research Associates, Teaching Assistants (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Dr. M. R. Kare and Dr. W. Medway with class, Undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Administrative Personnel
      - Brown, Robert Batson (Box 31, Folder 11)
        Assistant dean - administration
      - Edmonson, Katherine. (Box 31, Folder 12)
        Assistant dean - educational development, student services
      - Fowler, Ira (Box 31, Folder 13)
        Custodian
      - Griffith, Jeannie (Box 31, Folder 14)
        Staff writer
      - Haight, Helena H. (Box 31, Folder 15)
        Administrative manager
      - Hamilton, William (Box 31, Folder 16)
        Medical illustrator
      - Hendricks, Margaret A. "Peg" (Box 31, Folder 17)
        Assistant dean - public affairs and development
      - Huhta, Ina M. (Box 31, Folder 18)
        Accounts assistant
      - Kauber, Barbara M. (Box 31, Folder 19)
        Financial aid coordinator
      - Kelman, Eugenia (Box 31, Folder 20)
        Assistant dean - student services
      - Kent, Lindley C. (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Newson, Marion (Box 31, Folder 22)